<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Website</string>
    <string name="home_screen">Home</string>
    <string name="education_screen">Education</string>
    <string name="skills_screen">Skills</string>
    <string name="experience_screen">Experience</string>
    <string name="projects_screen">Projects</string>
    <string name="project_details_screen">Project Details</string>
    <string name="social_media_screen">Social Media</string>
    <string name="achievements_screen">Achievements</string>

    <string name="welcome_p1">Welcome to my</string>
    <string name="welcome_p2">digital portfolio!</string>

    <string name="homepage_description">I'm passionate about tech and focused on Android app development.</string>
    <string name="homepage_tutor_website">My tutoring website</string>

    <!-- COMMON -->
    <string name="main">Main</string>
    <string name="skills">Skills</string>
    <string name="projects">Projects</string>
    <string name="experience">Experience</string>
    <string name="education">Education</string>
    <string name="social_media">Social Media</string>
    <string name="achievements">Achievements</string>
    <string name="resume">Resumé</string>
    <string name="no_results">Could not find anything...</string>
    <string name="search_placeholder">Search...</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>

    <!-- HOME -->
    <string name="home_description">I am a passionate software developer with a focus on Android app development. Here, you can explore my skills, projects, and achievements.</string>
    <string name="skills_description">I have a diverse skill set in software development, including expertise in various programming languages, frameworks, and tools. My focus is on creating efficient and user-friendly applications.</string>
    <string name="projects_description">I have worked on a variety of projects, ranging from mobile applications to web development. Each project showcases my ability to solve complex problems and deliver high-quality software solutions.</string>
    <string name="experience_description">With experience in both commercial and academic projects, I have honed my skills in software engineering, project management, and teamwork. I am committed to continuous learning and professional growth.</string>
    <string name="education_description">I hold a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science from Jagiellonian University, where I gained a solid foundation in programming, algorithms, and software development methodologies.</string>
    <string name="social_media_description">Connect with me on social media to stay updated on my latest projects, achievements, and insights into the world of software development.</string>
    <string name="achievements_description">I have received several awards and recognitions for my contributions to software development and education. These achievements reflect my dedication to excellence and my passion for technology.</string>

    <string name="skills_button">Skills</string>
    <string name="projects_button">Projects</string>
    <string name="experience_button">Experience</string>
    <string name="education_button">Education</string>
    <string name="social_media_button">Social Media</string>
    <string name="achievements_button">Achievements</string>

    <string name="view_more">View More</string>

    <!-- SKILLS -->
    <string name="skills_title">Technical Skills</string>
    <string name="skills_subtitle">A collection of my programming languages, frameworks, and other technical skills.</string>

    <string name="programming_languages">Programming Languages</string>
    <string name="frameworks">Frameworks</string>
    <string name="markup_style">Markup &amp; Style</string>
    <string name="libraries">Libraries</string>
    <string name="languages">Languages</string>

    <string name="beginner">Beginner</string>
    <string name="competent">Competent</string>
    <string name="proficient">Proficient</string>
    <string name="advanced">Advanced</string>
    <string name="expert">Expert</string>
    <string name="native">Native</string>
    <string name="c1">C1</string>

    <!-- PROJECTS -->
    <string name="projects_title">Programming projects</string>
    <string name="projects_subtitle">A collection of my programming projects, showcasing my skills and experience in software development.</string>

    <string name="mobile_application">Mobile application</string>
    <string name="web_application">Web application</string>
    <string name="desktop_application">Desktop application</string>
    <string name="multiplatform_application">Multiplatform application</string>
    <string name="library">Library</string>
    <string name="console_application">Console application</string>
    <string name="game">Game</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>

    <string name="commercial_project">Commercial</string>
    <string name="academic_project">Academic</string>
    <string name="tools_project">Tools</string>
    <string name="practice_project">Practice</string>
    <string name="project_overview">Project Overview</string>

    <string name="screenshots">Screenshots</string>

    <string name="projects_master-system_description">This tournament management application was developed on commission to facilitate competitive match play according to a client-specific algorithm. The app provides a user-friendly interface for entering match results, automatically pairs teams for the next round based on the algorithm, calculates points, and generates comprehensive PDF summaries of the tournament's progress. Additionally, it creates graphs to visually represent the algorithm's logic and outcomes. The application is translated into four languages using Python's gettext module, ensuring accessibility for a diverse user base. This project showcases my ability to deliver tailored, multilingual software solutions that meet specific client requirements and enhance the management of complex tournament structures.</string>
    <string name="projects_master-system_shortDescription">Tournament management app with custom algorithm with many features</string>
    <string name="projects_vl_description">Valorant Lineups is a comprehensive mobile application tailored for Valorant players to enhance their in-game strategies. The app offers a vast collection of lineups, enabling players to execute advanced techniques without the need for extensive memorization. By providing real-time guidance and detailed instructions, Valorant Lineups streamlines the learning process and empowers players to perform at their best, improving both individual and team performance.</string>
    <string name="projects_vl_shortDescription">Mobile app for Valorant players to use in-game lineups</string>
    <string name="projects_demiurg_shortDescription">Text-based game creator and interpreter enabling users to design and play interactive narratives.</string>
    <string name="projects_demiurg_description">Demiurg is a comprehensive application developed as part of a Software Engineering course, created by a team of five. The project includes a robust game creator and interpreter for text-based games, allowing users to design intricate game worlds with advanced mechanics such as non-linear quests and dynamic storylines. The creator empowers users to craft detailed interactive narratives, while the interpreter provides an immersive experience for playing these games. This project showcases our collaborative effort and proficiency in software development, highlighting our ability to deliver sophisticated tools for creative expression.</string>
    <string name="projects_daymath_description">DayMath is a comprehensive educational application I developed independently during my university studies, targeting students in Polish primary and secondary schools. The app is designed to enhance mathematical learning through a variety of interactive features, including math quizzes, detailed textual explanations of various topics, and animations that visualize and clarify complex problems. These tools work together to provide an engaging and effective learning experience. Although the app is still a work in progress and has not been officially released, it represents my commitment to improving education through technology and my ongoing efforts to refine and expand its capabilities.</string>
    <string name="projects_daymath_shortDescription">Educational app for Polish students, featuring math quizzes, explanations, and animations.</string>
    <string name="projects_movie-ai_shortDescription">Desktop app recommending movies based on user ratings</string>
    <string name="projects_movie-ai_description">The Movie Recommendation System is a desktop application created in collaboration with a colleague as part of a Fundamentals of Artificial Intelligence course. This app enables users to rate movies they have watched, and employs AI algorithms to recommend new movies tailored to their preferences. By analyzing user ratings and employing sophisticated recommendation techniques, the system provides personalized movie suggestions, enhancing the user’s viewing experience. This project highlights our practical application of AI principles and our ability to develop user-centric, intelligent software solutions.</string>
    <string name="projects_generator-tabliczek_shortDescription">Application generating room number and name plates</string>
    <string name="projects_generator-tabliczek_description">This application was created in collaboration with a colleague for a programming course in C#. It generates room number and name plates that can be printed and hung next to room doors. The application allows users to choose the font, logo, and text color. It also enables saving the project between sessions.</string>
    <string name="projects_scheduler_shortDescription">Application for generating lesson schedules integrated with Discord.</string>
    <string name="projects_scheduler_description">This application was created to facilitate the organization of my tutoring sessions. It allows me to easily add new lessons to the schedule. The application is integrated with Discord, enabling me to automatically send notifications about new lessons to my server. It also automatically retrieves the current day of the year and generates a schedule for the upcoming week, allowing the user to set the starting day (e.g., today or tomorrow). It also allows: <br/>-setting the start and end time <br/>-choosing a theme <br/>-classifying individual lessons (exercises, lectures, tutoring sessions (remote or in-person), one-time events, etc.) <br/>-listing dates.</string>
    <string name="projects_binary-clock_shortDescription">Binary clock made using Compose Multiplatform</string>
    <string name="projects_binary-clock_description">Binary clock made using Compose Multiplatform</string>
    <string name="projects_subtitles-shifter_shortDescription">Simple script allowing to shift subtitles in .srt files</string>
    <string name="projects_subtitles-shifter_description">Simple script allowing to shift subtitles in .srt files. It was created for my individual need to shift subtitles that did not match the movie version (were delayed by a few seconds forward or backward).</string>
    <string name="projects_youtube-downloader_shortDescription">Multithreaded script allowing to download songs from YouTube</string>
    <string name="projects_youtube-downloader_description">This application allows you to download a playlist from Spotify, via YouTube. It requires the user to export the playlist to a .csv file using the Exportify application, and then downloads the songs from YouTube in separate threads, searching for them by name and artist, and saving them in an organized way - creating folders with artists, and naming each song with its title.</string>
    <string name="projects_tic-tac-toe_shortDescription">Simple Tic-Tac-Toe game that can be played with a friend on Discord</string>
    <string name="projects_tic-tac-toe_description">Simple Tic-Tac-Toe game that can be played with a friend on Discord</string>
    <string name="projects_crypto-tracker_shortDescription">App tracking cryptocurrency prices</string>
    <string name="projects_crypto-tracker_description">App tracking cryptocurrency prices. It allows adding cryptocurrencies to track, and displays their current prices along with a chart of changes over the last 24 hours.</string>

    <!-- EXPERIENCE -->
    <string name="experience_title">Experience</string>
    <string name="experience_subtitle">A collection of my professional experience, including tutoring and app development.</string>

    <string name="experience_tutor_title">Math Tutor</string>
    <string name="experience_tutor_description">Teaching mathematics to students</string>
    <string name="experience_app_developer_title">Commercial App Developer</string>
    <string name="experience_app_developer_description">Building and monetizing my own commercial applications</string>

    <string name="students_taught">Students taught</string>
    <string name="rating">Rating</string>
    <string name="reviews">Reviews</string>
    <string name="apps_published">Apps published</string>
    <string name="total_downloads">Total downloads</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="self-employed">Self-employed</string>
    <string name="commercial">Commercial</string>

    <string name="primary_technologies">Primary Technologies</string>

    <!-- EDUCATION -->
    <string name="education_title">Education</string>
    <string name="education_subtitle">A collection of my education, including my Bachelor's degree and high school.</string>

    <string name="education_uj_degree">Bachelor degree of Computer Science</string>
    <string name="education_uj_organization">Jagiellonian University</string>
    <string name="education_zsz_degree">IT Technician</string>
    <string name="education_zsz_organization">Zespół Szkół Zawodowych w Przeworsku</string>
    <string name="Poland">Poland</string>

    <string name="Algebra">Algebra</string>
    <string name="Computer Organization and Architecture">Computer Organization and Architecture</string>
    <string name="Programming">Programming</string>
    <string name="Logic and Set Theory">Logic and Set Theory</string>
    <string name="Mathematical Analysis">Mathematical Analysis</string>
    <string name="Programming Methods">Programming Methods</string>
    <string name="Operating Systems">Operating Systems</string>
    <string name="Algorithms and Data Structures">Algorithms and Data Structures</string>
    <string name="Discrete Mathematics">Discrete Mathematics</string>
    <string name="Databases">Databases</string>
    <string name="Software Engineering">Software Engineering</string>
    <string name="Probability and Statistics">Probability and Statistics</string>
    <string name="Computer Networks">Computer Networks</string>
    <string name="Formal Languages and Automata">Formal Languages and Automata</string>
    <string name="Numerical Methods">Numerical Methods</string>
    <string name="Functional Programming">Functional Programming</string>
    <string name="Android Programming">Android Programming</string>
    <string name="Design Patterns">Design Patterns</string>
    <string name="C# Programming">C# Programming</string>
    <string name="Cognitive Systems">Cognitive Systems</string>
    <string name="Cognitive Science">Cognitive Science</string>
    <string name="Web Programming">Web Programming</string>
    <string name="Fundamentals of AI">Fundamentals of AI</string>
    <string name="English">English</string>
    <string name="Networking">Networking</string>
    <string name="Hardware Maintenance">Hardware Maintenance</string>

    <string name="Certificate CCNA Routing and Switching Introduction to Networks">Certificate: CCNA Routing and Switching: Introduction to Networks</string>
    <string name="Certificate PCAP Programming Essentials in Python">Certificate: PCAP: Programming Essentials in Python</string>
    <string name="Certificate NDG Linux Unhatched">Certificate: NDG Linux Unhatched</string>
    <string name="Certificate Introduction to Cybersecurity">Certificate: Introduction to Cybersecurity</string>
    <string name="Certificate Cybersecurity Essentials">Certificate: Cybersecurity Essentials</string>
    <string name="Certificate Be Your Own Boss">Certificate: Be Your Own Boss</string>
    <string name="Certificate Get Connected">Certificate: Get Connected</string>
    <string name="Certificate Introduction to the Internet of Everything">Certificate: Introduction to the Internet of Everything</string>
    <string name="Certificate 3ds Max Animation">Certificate: 3ds Max Animation</string>
    <string name="Certificate 3ds Max Visualisation">Certificate: 3ds Max Visualisation</string>
    <string name="Certificate 3ds Max Modeling">Certificate: 3ds Max Modeling</string>
    <string name="Certificate EU Code Week">Certificate: EU Code Week</string>
    <string name="Certificate CPA Programming Essentials in C++">Certificate: CPA: Programming Essentials in C++</string>

    <string name="programming_and_software_engineering">Programming and Software Engineering</string>
    <string name="mathematics">Mathematics</string>
    <string name="systems_and_computer_technology">Systems and Computer Technology</string>
    <string name="ai_and_cognitive_science">AI and Cognitive Science</string>

    <string name="courses">Courses</string>
    <string name="professional_certificates">Professional Certificates</string>

    <plurals name="n_courses">
        <item quantity="one">%1$d course</item>
        <item quantity="other">%1$d courses</item>
    </plurals>

    <plurals name="n_certificates">
        <item quantity="one">%1$d certificate</item>
        <item quantity="other">%1$d certificates</item>
    </plurals>
    <!-- ACHIEVEMENTS -->
    <string name="achievements_title">Achievements</string>
    <string name="achievements_subtitle">A collection of my achievements, including awards and recognitions in various contests.</string>

    <string name="programming_competitions">Programming Competitions</string>
    <string name="math_competitions">Math Competitions</string>
    <string name="scholarships">Scholarships</string>
    <string name="other_achievements">Other Achievements</string>

    <string name="1st Place in the Independence Dictation Contest">1st Place in the Independence Dictation Contest</string>
    <string name="Przeworsk County Scholarship">Przeworsk County Scholarship</string>
    <string name="1st Place in the EXPERT Group at the PIX 2019 Contest - National School Programming Championship">1st Place in the EXPERT Group at the PIX 2019 Contest - National School Programming Championship</string>
    <string name="Qualification to the Semi-Finals of the Polish Edition of the International Pix Programming Challenge">Qualification to the Semi-Finals of the Polish Edition of the International Pix Programming Challenge</string>
    <string name="Honorable Mention in the National History Contest 'Krag'">Honorable Mention in the National History Contest "Krą"</string>
    <string name="2nd Place in the 24th Prof Jan Marszal Mathematics Contest for Middle Schools">2nd Place in the 24th Prof. Jan Marszał Mathematics Contest for Middle Schools</string>
    <string name="1st Place in the School Programming Contest">1st Place in the School Programming Contest</string>
    <string name="Honorable Mention in the 15th District Math Contest 'Procent'">Honorable Mention in the 15th District Math Contest "Procent"</string>
    <string name="1st Place in the 14th District Math Contest for Second-Year Middle School Students">1st Place in the 14th District Math Contest for Second-Year Middle School Students</string>
    <string name="2nd Place in the School English Contest">2nd Place in the School English Contest</string>
    <string name="Honorable Mention in the International Math Contest 'Kangur Matematyczny'">Honorable Mention in the International Math Contest "Kangur Matematyczny"</string>

    <string name="1st place">1st place</string>
    <string name="school">School</string>
    <string name="regional">Regional</string>
    <string name="national">National</string>
    <string name="international">International</string>
    <string name="district">District</string>

    <string name="n_achievements">%1$s achievements</string>


    <!-- Time -->
    <string name="january">January</string>
    <string name="february">February</string>
    <string name="march">March</string>
    <string name="april">April</string>
    <string name="may">May</string>
    <string name="june">June</string>
    <string name="july">July</string>
    <string name="august">August</string>
    <string name="september">September</string>
    <string name="october">October</string>
    <string name="november">November</string>
    <string name="december">December</string>

    <string name="now">Now</string>
    <plurals name="n_years">
        <item quantity="one">%1$d year</item>
        <item quantity="other">%1$d years</item>
    </plurals>

</resources>